

Contact

2

791 567 002



kasia.banas100@gmail.com



Wrocław



www.linkedin.com/in/katarzynabanaś-cv

Test certificate

ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level

Skills

Software testing

Playwright

Cypress

Selenium

Postman/Insomnia

DevTools

TypeScript

SQL

HTML

Jmeter

JIRA/Trello/Confluence

Katarzyna Banaś

Software Test Engineer

Hardworking and passionate individual with a very positive "can-do" attitude and 10 years of experience in the IT industry. Possesses excellent analytical thinking skills, a strong attention to detail and accuracy, and task-oriented teamwork abilities. Capable of creating innovative user interfaces as well as ensuring the stability and security of software products.

Professional Experience

O 01.2023 - 01.2024 GPW S.A. Quality Engineer

- Conducted manual and automated tests using Cypress and Playwright to ensure application quality.
- Developed and executed test scripts, test plans and test cases for software products.
- Identified, reported and tracked defects using bug tracking tools.
- Performed retest testing and regression testing to verify the resolution of defects and ensure software stability.
- Conducted RESTful API endpoint tests using Insomnia/Postman.
- Assisted in creating and maintaining test environments.
- Involved in creating performance tests using Jmeter and preparing test data.
- Participated in sprint planning, daily stand-ups, retrospectives and review as part of the Agile development process.
- Collaborated closely with developers, product owner and other stakeholders to understand requirements and provide feedback.

O 01.2013 - present

InOneCar.com Sp. z.o.o.

Product Manager

- Conducted market research and analyzed user needs to define requirements.
- Assembled a team of developers, UX/UI designers, marketing specialists, and other key roles necessary for project development.
- Created mockups and prototypes of web and mobile applications.
- Managed the backlog, prioritizing tasks and coordinating work with development team.
- · Conducted software tests and provided valuable feedback.
- Built strong collaborative relationships with development teem and external stakeholders.

GitLab

UXPin

Scrum/Agile

TestRail

Illustrator

Teamworking

Communication

Ability to work under pressure

Attention to detail

Languages

English (B1/B2)

Polish (Native)

Hobbies

Computer graphics

Running

Traveling

Carpooling activist

Cooking

O 05.2011 - 01.2013

Ditex Sp. z o.o.

Marketing and Sales Specialist

- Established contacts with new clients, prepared offers and contracts.
- Maintained company profiles on social networking sites and media.
- Updated the company website.
- Implemented and managed CRM processes.

O 05.2010 - 05.2011

Toshiba (Poland) Sp. z o.o.

Production Planning and Quality Assurance Specialist

- Prepared short and long-term production plans.
- Supervised production processes based on received orders and forecasted sales levels.
- Prepared comprehensive analyses and reports.
- Monitored the supply status of the production plant.

O 12.2008 - 10.2009

EPP Sp. z o.o.

Production Planning Specialist

- Created production schedules in the production plant.
- Planned and organized workflows for multiple products.
- Collaborated with other departments on production goals and schedules.
- Managed inventory, rescheduled tasks, and resolved cancellation issues
- Supported the maintenance of planned orders in line with the company's monthly forecast.

Education

0 10.2021 - 06.2022

WSB Merito University Wroclaw

• Master of Software Tester for Mobile and Server Applications

O 10.2003 - 06.2008

Wroclaw University of Science and Technology

- Master of Engineering for Organization and Design of Transport Systems
- Master of Engineering for Quality Management (in Logistics)

09.1999 - 06.2003

Secondary School No. 2 in Oleśnica

O 09.1991 - 06.1999

Primary School No. 1 in Oleśnica